fansonline.net 2008-05-15

# FansOnline.net || The UK's Only Independent Fans Network

**TERMS OF USE AND PRIVACY POLICY

This website is protected by international Copyright. Copying, duplication or reproduction of content by any means whatsoever is strictly prohibited without the prior written permission of FansOnline.net.

**

Commercial Exploitation: The information contained herein, including text, images and photographs, must not be copied,adapted, distributed or otherwise used for commercial gain. Any such action would establish liability for a civil action and may give rise to criminal proceedings.

None-Commercial Use: Where permission is sought for the purposes of communication and knowledge sharing only, that is with no possibility of commercial gain, then permission will normally be given - providing that FansOnline.net is acknowledged as the source of such information.

© FansOnline.net 2007 All rights reserved.

FansOnline.net wish to recognise and acknowledge that some of the material contained herein has been contributed by visitors to the site. Material so submitted is automatically Copyright protected in the name of the contributor - and must not be used, commercially or none-commercially, without the Copyright owner's permission.

This site in no way wishes to infringe on anyone's copyright. It is our policy to make every effort to respect the copyrights of outside parties. If you believe that your copyright has been misused, please email us and we will remove the picture(s) or acknowledge the source, as soon as we receive your email. In view of this, please do not submit any material to us that you do not hold copyright over or have permission to distribute freely.

The views expressed on this site are the personal opinions of the site authors, columnists and message board posters and do not necessarily represent the views of the respective clubs.

FansOnline.net accepts no responsibility for the content of or the use made of information provided directly or indirectly by this site or by sites which this site links to, and shall not be held liable in respect of any loss suffered therefrom. It is our policy to discourage illegal use of this facility. Whilst every effort is made to avoid listing links to sites that in any way encourage hooliganism or contain other violent, pornographic or illegal material (as defined by legislation in Belgium the United Kingdom and the European Union), the vast amount of links makes it impossible to monitor changes on each and every one of the sites to which this site links. Should you come across a site that contains material that is in violation of this policy, we would be happy to hear from you so that we may remove the respective link.

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The operator of this website, Waking Lion, is committed to protecting your privacy. Please take a moment to read this Privacy Policy. References to "we", "us" and "our" in this Policy are references to FansOnline.net. This Policy describes what happens to the information which you supply to us, where that information identifies you individually :- e.g. your name and address details. 

We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time.

**What information do we hold about you and how is it collected?**

When you register on this site, some personal information (including your name and email addresses) is collected by us. You may also be asked for your personal information at other times on this site - in connection with activities such as competitions, polls, voting etc.

Unlike many other online services, we do not use "cookies" to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data sent from the server and stored on your PC's hard drive. Most web browsers are automatically set up to accept cookies, but you can set your browser to refuse cookies or ask your browser to show you where a cookie has been set up. Certain services are only activated by the presence of a cookie and, if you choose to refuse cookies, all features of this site will still be available to you.

**What do we do with your personal information?**

We will store your email address in order to help us to provide you with a more personalised service which is tailored to suit your needs. You will receive emails from us for the following purposes:

(i) to update and develop records and for assessment and analysis including market and service/product analysis;

(ii) to assist in the provision of services/products to you;

(iii) to facilitate reviews, developments and improvements to the services/products offered to you.

(iv) to notify you of new articles published on FansOnline.net.

Please rest assured that FansOnline.net will never pass your email address to any third party.

**By law, you are entitled to:**

(i) object to your personal information being used for marketing purposes. Should you not wish to receive emails from FansOnline.net, simply inform us and your email address will be removed from the list.

(ii) receive, upon request, a copy of any personal information about you which is held by us.

(iii) require the rectification, erasure or blocking of any of your personal information which is inaccurate or not up to date held by us.

If you wish to exercise any of these rights, or if you wish to opt-out of any future processing of your personal information held by us, then please write to me, Steve Goldby, at the contact address set out below stating your full name and address and providing any other relevant information.

**When does this Privacy Policy not apply?**

This Privacy Policy only applies to the collection of data by us and the use of that data by us. It does not cover third party sites to which we provide links, nor does it cover advertisers and content partners within our service who may also collect your personal information. They may have their own privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of use.

**Disclaimer:** FansOnline.net accept no legal responsibilty and cannot be held accountable for the content and accuracy of postings on the New Holgate Message Board.

**How do we protect your information?**

FansOnline.net is firmly committed to data security. When you place orders, we offer use of a secure server. The secure server software encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. We take steps to guard against unauthorised access to customer data. Although we make every effort to create a secure environment for your personal information, we cannot guarantee the safety of any personal information which you transmit to us online.

**Contacting us.**

If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information please write to:

FansOnline.net  
Suite 4  
Moray House   
258 Marton Road  
Middlesbrough   
TS4 2EZ
